

- +46 762 876 674
- zhuhuadan@gmail.com

https://zhuhuadan.com

- https://github.com/MikoZhu https://www.linkedin.com/in/hua dan-zhu-802864134/
- Stockholm, Sweden

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Bootcamp Udemy(online) Sep 2022 - Sep 2023

Python and C#
Hermods Yrkeshögskola(Sweden)
Mar 2021 - Sep 2021

Master of HR Business and Management Aston University(UK) 2017 - 2018

EXPERTISE

HTML CSS/SCSS Tailwind
Javascript React Node.js Python
Express.js MongoDB Authentication
Agile Methodology MySQL
Figma Canva Photoshop

LANGUAGE

English
Swedish(SVA 2)
Chinese

HUADAN ZHU(MIKO)

Front-End || Full-Stack Developer

ABOUT ME

Huadan is a talented developer who is embarking on a career transition from human resources management (HRM) to web development. With a master's degree and seven years of experience in HRM, I have developed strong skills in adaptability, a growth mindset, and the confidence to tackle new challenges. As a web developer, I am excited to leverage these qualities to solve complex problems, continue exploring new skills, and further improve as a developer.

EXPERIENCE

O June 2023- Jan 2024

Technigo, Sweden

Web Development

Completed a rigorous 22-week coding boot camp, dedicated over 2,000 hours for coding. Gained proficiency in JavaScript (ES 6), React, HTML5, CSS, server-side programming with Node.js, MongoDB, and authentication mechanisms. Completed over 24 projects covering everything from the basics of programming to structuring web projects using the latest technology.

O Dec 2020 - Sep 2021

SHEIN, Sweden

Client Service

At SHEIN, a fast fashion company, I achieved a 98% customer satisfaction rate. Proficient in CSM, I managed 60+ daily tickets with 99% accuracy, emphasizing seamless Swedish customer experiences in logistics and returns.

Sep 2017 - Sep 2019

UCNEST, London

Marketing and Recruiter

At a startup tech company, I recruited and trained over 30 professionals, catalyzing organizational growth. In the realm of Marketing & Customer Service, I achieved 100% sales success with a 10% contribution from customer service while expanding into the Chinese market through trend-savvy, multichannel strategies.

Aug 2014 - Oct 2016

World International English, China Regional HR Manager

Screened over 100 candidates and conducted 20 phone interviews daily, resulting in the recruitment of 500+ professionals, including key leaders. Orchestrated coaching programs to foster growth and aligned HR with strategic management to achieve business goals.

Feb 2013 - Jun 2014

SRE Group, China

HR Supervisor

Managed HR across multiple locations, overseeing monthly interviews for 150+candidates and achieving annual onboarding exceeding 100. Implemented competitive reward and payroll strategy, executed organization-wide HR functions, integrating KPIs, 360 assessments, SMART goals, and a performance management system.